Hello Kanchan ji and my greetings to Amit ji also.
Tell me what is my question?  My question is,
I have 100 shares of ICICI LBA, ICICI
LBD
at ₹1500, I have this IPO since the time of IPO,
this
IPO is very old, I have it since the IPO came seven-eight years ago
and this is
my average share at ₹1500, I
have 100 shares, I
want to know the opinion about ICICI Loan Bar,
I want to hold it for long term, I want to
hold it for the next 10 years,
but will it give returns, will it go up
or will it remain here.
Ok.  Definitely, its IPO came in 2017
and its listing was seen around 680.
After that,
we have seen a descent amount and a
descent rally has been seen in it.  But your
question is how much higher does it have the potential to go from here.  The
purchase
is for Rs 1500 and 100 shares are currently
in your portfolio.  Today, even in a falling
market, we are seeing a good momentum
in ICC LBT.
Amit ji, what do you think?  Looking at the future treasury, at
this time, a
profit of around ₹400 per share
is visible.  What numbers
can we expect to see next?  Should it be held or should the little
profit be
partially retained?
No, ICICI Lar should be held.
Because if we look at the weekly charts, the
stock is at a good support.  There was
a run up in this stock.  After that it
went into a bit of sideways consolidation.  But overall it is
positive.  Consolidation is
not a problem yet.  Their outlook is
extremely long term.  So
place a stop loss of 1800.  If you ask
when will a bullish trend form here, that will only happen
once the stock
trades above 1960 1975 levels and
sustains a stop loss of 1800, then
I think that
near term targets of 2100 2150
are possible here slowly but steadily.
OK, the advice is to hold ICICI LMB,
we are seeing a lot of momentum here.
Today, in fact, the entire insurance space
is trading with a rally and
targets up to 2150 are being seen.  You should
maintain a stop loss of Rs 1800.